Tufts Criterion UP053
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Criterion, 1968 -- 1993; UP053.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 8 Volumes
  - Criterion, December, 1978; UP053.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    [Alumni association] election results; Michael R. Alberi (A74) Married Lorraine Parish (E77), civil en. in MO. Richard Alexander (D 74 G 76) Opening office in Merrimack, NH. [Alfaro, Gustavo A.] New chairman of Dept. of Romance Languages. Carol Ali (A77) Working for First National Bank in Boston. Dr. Myron Allukian (A60) Won the Alfred L. Frechette Award, p. 18; [Alumni council] Election results
  - Criterion, February, 1979; UP053.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
    Richards B. M. Abrams [F72, F78]. Student Boston College Law School. Academic Records; false academic credentials; P.3.. Randolph K. Adams. Graduated from squandron officer school, Maxwell Air Force Base, Alabama. Louis Alfano (M.D.) Elected chairman of board of Blue Shield of MA. Clarke Allard (A65) Living in Havanah, Cuba. Deborah L. Allison (A72) Elected VV.p. of Wellington Management Co.
  - Criterion, 1979-05-01; UP053.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Criterion, July, 1979; UP053.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni weekend] Photos; Jeffrey Adams (A 1970). Death of, May 25, 1979. Killed, crash of DC-10, Chicago; Eight men and two women elected to alumni council
  - Criterion, November, 1979; UP053.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
    [Alumni relations] Formation of new offices; Susan Whilton Agusti [F1978]. Promoted in Center for Strategi and International Studies, Georgetown University.
  - Criterion, March, 1980; UP053.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Tad Akiba [Faculty]. Hibakusha: Survivors of atomic bombings (incl. photo). David C. Albert (A76) Recieved M.S. from Graduate School, Hahnemann Hospital, Philadelphia. Death of John E, Alcott (A1921), 8/10/78. Death of (8/8/76) Joeseph J. Alen (T 1961).
  - Criterion, June, 1980; UP053.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] Group travel offered; Inside says July. Herbert Abrams (M 1935). Death of, March 15, 1980. Odeh F. Abudene [F 1968]. Vice Presidency, First National Bank of Chicago.; Administration 1980. Michael A. Hoffman named executive vice-president (includes photo). [Akiba, Tad] (Faculty) Letters commenting on Akiba's "Hibakusha" article in March Criterion. Edith (Bach) Allen (A1973) Ph.D. recieved from University of Wyoming, Jan. 1980.
  - Criterion, September, 1980; UP053.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Paul M. Acker (A 1974). Receives Fulbright-Hays travel grant to Ireland.; Death of Edward J. Acton [M 1947], June 4, 1980. p. 29; [Adler, Deborah L. A '76] Made fellow of society of Actuaries. P. 24.
  - Criterion, November, 1980; UP053.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Tad Akiba [Faculty] Letter supporting Akiba; First alumni college planned for June
  - Criterion, March, 1981; UP053.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni/ae college explores ethnic history; [Alumni/ae] Performers reunite: Tufts Symphonic band and torn ticket host alumni reunions; [Alumni/ae] Alums can enjoy conferences, classes at Talloires campus; [Alumni office] Alumni college explores ethnic history; [Alumni council] Reports progress in standing committees; Appointed Bangladesh ambassador to Italy. Louis F. Alfano (M1946) re-elected chairman Blue Shield of Massachusetts. [Alumni 1981] Nominating committee reports on alumni trustee ballot, p. 11.
  - Criterion, July, 1981; UP053.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Frederick N. Acford (E 1937). Death of: November 9, 1980. J. Byron Fleck (Fletcher 1976) Promoted in Westinghouse Electric, p 26. Warren L. Adams (D 1919). Death of: November 20, 1980.; Marco A. Aguilar [F1977]. Promoted in Seguros Bancomer, S.A., Mexico. [Alumni 1981] Alumni notes, p. 14-15.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1982; UP053.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] News briefs from Alumni association [includes photos]; Mitchel Abolafia (A74) earned doctorate from SUNY, Stonybrook. p. 23; [Admissions] Admissions and SAT scores up. p. 3.; [Agar, Robert K.] Death of: March 31, 1981.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1982; UP053.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. What is alumni council; Changes in alumni association; Continuing education spring program set [Alumni association]; Alumni association awards demystified; [Alumnae] Presidents ball in Wessell library; Death of Sidney B. Altman [D1920] October 1980; [Alumni 1982] AIESEC [L'Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Commerciales] Seeks alumni help, p 7; [Accreditation, Vet School] TUSVM [Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine] gets provisional accreditation. p. 4; [Agam, Hasmy Bin-F'81] Named acting head, center for International Relations and Diplomacy, Malaysia, p. 28. [Aisner, Mark (M 1935) Appointed Massachusetts Board of Registration. [Alumni 1982] Alumni association awards demystified, p. 6-7. [Alumni 1982] Alumni/ae over 60 asked to participate in nutritions study, p. 6. [Alumni 1982] Changes in alumni association, pg. 6. [Alumni 1982] Continuing educaton spring program set, p. 7. [Alumni 1982] Mastrovita, Robert P. and Stepanian, Ira named Alumni Trustees, p. 3. [Alumni 1982] What is alumni council?, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1982; UP053.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Tufts-in-Italy reunion; Alumni weekend; Criterion survey; Alumni association presents annual awards; [Alumni association] Association elects officers to council
  - Criterion, Summer, 1982; UP053.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Notes on alumni day; [Alumni council] Tufts service citation recieved by eight; [Alumni council] Association elect officers; [Alumni association] Twelve graduates recieve senior awards; Robert W. Abbott (M 1940). Death of: March 27, 1982. Ann (Rice) Ach (E-P 1943). Death of: September 13, 1982. Harold Acres III (A 1964). Elected vice president, Bank of New Hampshire.; [Admissions] Tufts to enroll 1275 new students. p. 3. Akinwande B. Akinyemi (f 1965) Appointed professor, University of Lagos (Nigeria). Louis F. Alfano (M1946) re-appointed Massachusetts rate-setting commission policy review board. Death of (12/30/81) Clarence Allen (A'24 D'28). [Alumni 1982] Alumni Art show under consideration, p. 7. [Alumni 1982] Council, Association elect officers, p. 7. [Alumni 1982] Elected alumni/ae trustees, p. 6. [Alumni 1982] Need for activities funding, p. 7. [Alumni 1982] Notes on alumni day, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1982; UP053.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Peggy Lynn Abrams [BSOT 1974]. Resident in physical medicine and rehabilitation at Thomas Jefferson University in Phila. Linda (Elowitch) Abromson [J 1961]. Elected and sworn in as new mayor of Portland, ME. Accas, Eugene A.; Retired from Leo Burnett, USA; moved to L.A.; working as consultant in advertising and public relation; P.22. Wlater L. Adams (E 1920). Death of, March 31, 1980.; Alberto Agurcia [F76]. Announces birth of daughter, Sarah Lindsay, March 7, 1982. They live in Tegucigalpa, Honduras.; Susan Whilton Agusti [F77,F78] Announces birth of daughter, Caroline Demblans on March 15. Susan is consultant with Arthur D. Little.; Carol Ai [1977]. Works as account supervisor at Starr, McCombs, Koch Advertising in Honolulu; Ramon E. Alonso [F68] Senior Vice President of real estate development at Charlton Consolidated Corp. [Alumni 1982] First reunion for European alumni/ae at Talloires, p. 7. [Alumni 1982] Former provost assumes new alumni duties (Robert Shira), p. 6. [Alumni 1982] Homecoming '82: a Jumbo weekend, p.6. [Alumni 1982] Photoessay, p. 8. [Alumni 1982-83] Tufts club of Cape cod installs new officers, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1983; UP053.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    [Alumni relations] Search open for new director; Continuing education committee of alumni council announces schedule; [Alumni council] Communication committee seeks input; [Alumni association] By laws revisited; [Alumnae] Jackson women follow tradition of service [photo]; Donald B. Altvater moved with wife Frances [Connors, J1969] and daughter Laura to Reston, VA where he works for GTE; Porter S. Abbott (E 1914). Died 8/24/82 in Stoneham, MA.; Charles E. Adams (F1962) (A61) Vice principal of junior-senior high school in Manchester, MA. p. 22. Richard L. Abbott (1967). Guest lecturer last June at a nationwide opthamology symposium in the People's Republic of China. Richard Abrams [F 1977]. Attorney; financial investment reporter for "LOOK" t.v. program.; Stephen Ahearn [1981]. Married Hollis Greenspan (J81), August 22, 1982, in New Jersey; he earned second degree in mechanical engineering. Frank L. Alciere (A1922) (G22) Died 9/19/82 in Quincy, MA. [Alumni 1983] Hillel forms alumni group, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1983; UP053.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    Works of alumni/ae at Gallery 11; [Alumni weekend] Plans for alumni weekend; [Alumni council] Elections for alumni officers; [Alumni council] Adventure in Egypt; Annual alumni association awards announced; Stephen L. Adams (1972). Announces birth of third child. Steve is an associate director for Source EDP. [Ajamian, Diane] (1980) Working in Trust Division of Boston Investment Bank. [Alberti, Frank] (1965) Promoted to associate professor at University of Lowell. Death of (11/6/82) Gustav A. Aldrin (D1926) in Worcester, MA. Dr. Myron Allukian Jr. (1960) Dentist, elected to the executive board of the American Public Health Association, p. 23. [Alumni 1983] Adventure in Egypt, p.8. [Alumni 1983] Annual alumni associationi awards announced, p.8. [Alumni 1983] Beelzebub reunion, p. 7. [Alumni 1983] Medical, dental schools celebrate annual reunions, p. 8. [Alumni 1983] Reminiscences of class reunion, p.6. [Alumni 1983] Reunion: European Style, p. 6, 7.
  - Criterion, Summer, 1983; UP053.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    [Alumni weekend] Plans for alumni weekend; [Alumni relations] Fred Nickless named acting director of alumni relations; [Alumni association] Service citation presented to Maurene Golden and Richard A. Littlefield; [Alumnae] Jackson women networking; Robert A. Alukonis [A1958] new executive vice president and chief operations officer of Grobet File Co. of America, Inc., Carlstadt NJ; [Youssif Al-Fadel Al-Sabah] Chairman of the Gas and Petroleum Co. of Kuwait, was member of the faculty of the Salzburg Seminar held in Austria Feb. 27- March 12; [Admissions, Office of, 1983] Applications bigger and better; [Aghjayan, Edward K.] Appointed dierctor of the Electric Utility in Austin, TX, p. 19.; Mohiuddin Ahmad [F1954]. Assigned to the United Nations as senior political affairs officer in the office of the United Nations commisioner for Manibia. Ellen Albanese (1971) Editor of the "Country Gazette" which serves five towns in southern MA. [Alumni 1983] Adventure in Egypt, p. 6. [Alumni 1983] Alumni dance program, p. 7. [Alumni 1983] Election results announced, p. 6. [Alumni 1983] Keeping old friends: Golden Graduates, p.5. [Alumni 1983] Nickless, Fred named acting director of alumni relations, p. 5. [Alumni 1983] Reunion: European Style, p. 7. [Alumni 1983] Scholarships instituted for alumni families, p. 5.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1983; UP053.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    [Alumni council] Plans Egyptian tour; [Alumni council] Continuing education fall series; [Alumnae] Holly Ball becomes Holiday on the Hill; Roger Altreuter [1976] married Martha Mary Starkweather in Old Greenwich, CT; John Richard Ackerman (1975). Received Ph.D. in chemistry from Wesleyan University; [Adler, David D.; D '37] Death of, 3/20/83 in New Rochelle, NY. P. 30. Kathy Acketman (J 1978). Feature with photo. Jonathan Addleton (F 1983). Received Shell Fellowship for study in India.; Mohammad Yusof Ahmad [F1983]. Senior project officer of National Institute of Public Administration in Selangor, Malaysia. David Aisenberg (1982). Attending Villanova University Law School in PA. [Alumni 1983-84] Alumni art show, p. 7.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1984; UP053.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    Ronald Brinn new director of alumni relations [includes photo]; Death of Isadore Altman [M1932] on 7/23/86 in North Attleboro, MA; Death of Abraham H. Alter [D1928] on 11/26/82 at sea; Robert L. Abbott (E 15). Death of: July, 15 1983, in Seminole, Florida.; Mitchel Abolafia (A74) moved to Ithaca, NY where he is an assistant professor in Graduate School of Management at Cornell University p. 26. Jody Acford (1977). Married Steve Burgay (A78) September 4, in Goddard Chapel; she is an attorney at the Boston law firm of Hale and Dorr.; Admissions, Office of, 1984] The admissions game. (photos); Alice (Oleary) Ahern [J35]. Death of, August 11, 1983, in Eastham, MA. David Albert (1976) Assistant administrator of Martins Run Life Care Community. Michael J. Album (1975) Attorney in NYC. Death of (4/28/83) Arsham Alemian (M 33) in Orleans, MA. Steve M. Allison (1972) Working on doctoral thesis in clinical psychology and on staff on Boundaries Therapy Center in Acton, MA. [Alumni 1984] Identify with Tufts, p. 7.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1984; UP053.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    [Alumni weekend] Mayoralty revived [photos]; Anna (Thurman) Abrams (D19). Death of: 1/12/84. Howard Abrams (M74). Spoke on "The Resiliency of the Jewish Psyche."; [Adzigian, David (1962)] Vice President of government sales for Rediffusion Simulation, Inc. p. 18.; [Adzigian, Linda (Richards) J62] Moved to Dallas, TX from Binghamton, NY. p. 18.; Susan Whilton Agusti [F77] Announces birth of dag daughter, Olivia Lafitte Agusti on February 3, 1983.; Gary D. Ahlquist [1975]. Married Susan Kyle Rife; He is a senior associate in the Chicago office of Booz, Allen and Hamilton. Orlando J. Albani Jr. (USAF) (1971) Maintenance staff officer at Barksdale Air Force Base, LA. Death of (10/7/83) John H. Almy (D23) in Rhode Island. [Alumni 1984] Alumni Association awards presented for following: Distinguished Service Awards (5), Tufts Service Citations (4), Seniors Awards (12), p. 6. [Alumni 1984] Mayoralty revived, p. 6. [Alumni 1984] President's Ball: Photoessay, p. 7. [Alumni 1984] Tufts Gay Community (TGC) alumni reunion, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Summer, 1984; UP053.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    [Alumni/ae]Officer elections results; Academic sampler launches new program, New alumni club in France [includes photo], New York; [Alumni weekend] Academic sampler launches new program; [Alumni council] Officer election results; [Alumni council] Milauskas [Ronald] elected to dual alumni presidencies; [Alumni association] Milauskas (Ronald) elected to dual alumni presidencies [includes photograph]; Lawrence Altman [M1932] brings medicine to the public via the New York Times; William Abrams [A 1975]. New York alums make the news (photos).; [Adulyadej, Bhumibol (King of Thailand)] Mayer to present honorary degree to King of Thailand. p. 3; [Aghjayan, Edward] manager of the Snohomish County (WA) Public Utility District with headquarters in Everett, p. 22. [Akashi, Yasushi] Under-secretary-general of the United Nations Dept. of Public Information, guest speaker at Humanist Society of Metropolitan N.Y.. [Akiba, Tad] (faculty) Appointed senior fellow of the Nikkei Industry Research Institute of Japan. Robert L. Albright (G72) Inaugurated as the 11th president of Johnson C. Smith University in Charlotte, NC.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1984; UP053.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. New alumni relations team announced; [Alumni council] Sponsors east Africa tour; Highlights of alumni college [includes photos]; Charles E. Adams (F62) new principal of Cony High School in Augusta, ME. p. 23 John O. Alden (M46) Named vice president of life underwriting for Aetna Life and Casualty's Personal Financial Security Division. Joseph Ali (1967) Recipient of a commendation medal from the U.S. Public Health Service. Joseph J. Allegro (1955) Recieved a master of science degree in civil engineering from Northeastern University; [Ramon E. Alonso F68] President of Environmental Developers, Inc. (ED) of Aurora, CO. [Alumni 1984] Gittlemans to speak to California alumni, p. 6. [Alumni 1984] Graduate school fair welcomes alumni, p. 6.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1985; UP053.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Dwight R. Ambach] Councilman in Chevy Chase, MD. and dean of the school of area studies at Foreign Service Institute, as well as minister-couselor in senior foreign service; [Alumni/ae] Spring continuing education; [Alumni/ae] Innovations enhance traditions; [Alumni/ae] Student alumni links, Honoring Tuftonia's day; [Alumni weekend] Innovations enhance traditions; Charles E. Adams (F62) new principal of Cony High School in Augusta, ME. p. 22. Clifford Abbott (A69). Received 1983-84 Founders Association Award from University of Wisconsin at Green Bay. (page 23) David Albert (1976) Announces birth of son, Joshua Benjamin, on April 8. Carolyn Allen (Bliss) (1946) Appointed acquisitions administrator at the American Antiquarian Society.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1985; UP053.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Paris and Talloires trip planned; [Alumni/ae] Mayer addresses alumni council and European alumni; [Alumni weekend] Article re: jukebox poster [photo]; Mayer addresses alumni council; Walter Althof died 9/5/83; Dave Acheson (1976) Working in the geophysics field at Chevron in New Orleans. Ruby L. Adams (E-P 1932). Died October 18, 1884.; [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Over 10,000 apply to Tufts.; [Adzigian, Nazareth A38 M42] Died August 18, 1984. p. 30. [Albano, Leonard 1982] Structural engineer at Stone and Webster Engineering Co. in Boston, married Kathleen Baskin, (J84 E 84) 9/29/84 in Burlington, MA.
  - Criterion, Summer, 1985; UP053.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni weekend; [Alumni day] Alumni association recognizes valuable service to university [Distinguished service award][Tufts service citation][Seniors awards]; [Alumni council] Names new officers, Six new Tufts alumni council members were chosen; [Alumni council] Members contributed enough money to print 2,000 new copies of "Light on the Hill"; [Alumni college] Journey to France, June 11-22, 1985 [includes photos]; [Alumni association] New tradition: Tuftonia's day; [Alumni association] Names officers; [Alumni association] Honors six for service to Tufts: Richard W. Ballow, Linda Dixon [J1963], Elias Dow [M1953], Janet (Getchell) Manzelli [J1950], Robert Meehan [A1955], Thomas Swift [A1959][D1963]; Alumni association presents annual awards; Robert (Gilman) Adams (A 30). Death of, February 22, 1985. Trudy Albinger-Bixby (J77) Sailing around the world with her husband, Ethan Bixby.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1985; UP053.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Black alumni unite; [Alumni council] Alumni program: Paradox of masculinity [including photo]; David Adamson (F 73). United States foreign service officers assigned to the political section of the American Embassy in Panama. Orlando J. Albani (G73) Major Albani assumed commmand at Castle Air Force Base in CA. Death of (7/10/85) Jane L. Alexander (E-P 62) in Newton MA. Death of (1/3/85) William G. Allen (F50).
  - Criterion, Winter, 1986; UP053.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. A-Maze-ing alumni weekend; Death of Peter R. Amato [M1961]; [Alumni weekend] Plans for alumni weekend; [Alumni relations] New associate director joins alumni staff; Alumni college participants circle globe: Li-Li Chen led third alumni college class on sea-faring exploration of China aboard the Pearl of Scandinavia; Odeh E. Abudene. Senior vice president and brach manager of the Arab Bank Limited, New York branch. Jonathan Addleton (F 82). Married Fiona Riach, August 17, 1985; He is assigned to th program office at U.S aid mission in Islamabad, Pakistan. [Akiba, Tadatoshi (Faculty)] represented with two other faculty members Norbert Wiener Forum of Tufts at joint meeting in Tokyo last summer. Janet Allaire (D83) Private dental practitioner in Danvers, MA., married Marc. A. Greer (D 83) Sept. 4. [Alumni 1986] Alumni college participants circle globe; Continuing education spring series; A-Maze-ing Alumni Weekend planned; Jackson college Association of Tufts Alumnae offer career day symposium; Nutrition grads assemble for first time; Historical market site for Tufts Club of Boston, p. 20-21. [Alumni 1986] New associate director for Alumni staff (Eileen Schell), p. 20-21.
  - Criterion, Spring, 1986; UP053.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni weekend] Photoessay; [Alumni association] Helen (Dobbin) Taylor [J1936] added to the list of Tufts service citations recipients; [Alumni association] Distinguised service awards recipients: Bernard Berman [A1945][M1948], Lois (Leiper) DiLorenzo [J1943], Elizabeth (Van Houysen) Mayer (wife of president); Norton Nickerson (faculty), Barry J. Rosenbaum [A1960];Alumni association presents annual awards; Marguerite Abbot (BSOT 25). Death of, 7/28/85. (page 29); Dental School wins accreditation p. 4. Freeland Abbott (former faculty). Class of 1942 Prize Scolarship founded by Grant and Elaine Curtis in honor of Abbott and four other employees at Tufts. Former chief resident in Dept. of Dentistry at Yale-New Haven Hospital now participating in the oral and Maxillofacial surgery training program at Hosipital of St. Raphael in New Haven, CT. [Karen S. Ablow] p. 28; [Admissions, Office of] Tufts appoints new dean of admissions, David Cuttino. p. 4. Orlando J. Albani Jr. (1971) (G 1973) Awarded Air Force Commendation Medal at Castle AFB in California. Myron Allukian Jr. (1960) Elected chairman of the MA Board of Registration in Dentistry; He is the assistant deputy commisioner and director of community dental programs for Boston Department of Health and Hospitals, p. 24. [Alumni 1986] Alumni Association presents annual awards, p. 19. [Alumni 1986] Chemical Engineering grads hold reunion, p.21. [Alumni 1986] New York area alums enjoy "renaissance," p. 21. [Alumni 1986] Photoessay, p. 8-9. [Alumni 1986] Sponsors activities, p. 19. [Alumni 1986] Tuftonia's Day, 1986; Tuftonia's Day celebration grows, p. 20.
  - Criterion, Summer, 1986; UP053.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. David C, Albert ('76) Announces birth of second child, Elizabeth Anne, 12/85. David Allen ('76) Epidemic intelligence officer for Division of Reproductive Health at Centers for Disease Control in Atlanta.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1986; UP053.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Sandra Coifi named alumni secretary, Forming alliance: a learning experience; [Alumni relations] Sandra Ciolfi names alumni secretary; [Alumni association] Sandra Ciolfi named alumni secretary; William Altman [A1923[[M1927] died on 6/2/86 in Boston; [Phillip Alston] Elected as independent expert member of the newly established U.N. Committee on Economic Social and Cultural Rights; Judith [Landon] Alpert [1966] Editor of book titled Psychoanalysis andf Women: Contemporary Reappraisals. Ambassador of Papua New Guinea to the US and Mexico and permanent representative to the U.N. High Commissioner to Canada [Kiatro Abisinito] p. 28. [Aijala, Armas] Died 6/17/86 in Lewes, Del. Ellen Albanese (1971) Homored by the International Society of Weekly Newspaper Editors for excellence in editorial writing.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1987; UP053.001.008.00002 (Box 8)